Hello friends,
welcome to the channel. In today's video, we are going to
see the results of ICICI Lombard.
ICICI Lombard has also declared a dividend. A
dividend of ₹ has been declared on every equity share
and its record date is 27th October and
it is going to be paid to all the shareholders by 10th November.
All these figures are
in lakh rupees. We will convert it into crores. So,
if we talk about revenue or total income, the
total income has been Rs 5049 crore
in this quarter, which was Rs
4538 crore in the previous quarter and Rs 4499 crore in the same quarter of last year.
If we look at it on a quarter-on-quarter
basis, the total income has
increased by 11% and if we look at it on a year-on-year basis, the
income has increased by 12%.
If we talk about total expenses, the
total expenses
in this quarter have been Rs 4452 crore, which was Rs 4452 crore in the previous quarter.  It was worth Rs
4206 crore and in the same quarter of last year it was worth Rs
3988 crore.
If we look at it on a quarter to quarter basis,
we are seeing a growth of 5.85%
in expenses and if we look at it on a year on year basis, the
expenses have increased by 11.6%.
If we talk about net profit, there has been a
net profit of Rs 577 crore
in this quarter, which was Rs 390 crore in the previous quarter
and Rs 590 crore in the same quarter of last year.
If we
look at it on a quarter to quarter basis, the
net profit has increased by 48% and if we look at it on a year to year
basis, the net profit has decreased by 2.2%.
If you look at the EPS, the
EPS which was Rs 12.03 has decreased and the EPS has been Rs 11.75
in this quarter. If you
want to study the segment wise results, then you can pause the video here and
study the segment wise results. So that's all
in this video. If
you find this video informative  If you liked it then don't forget to
like the video and subscribe to the channel.
Jai Hind.